tonedeaf.com.au 2019-12-26

# The Brag Media Privacy Policy - The Brag Media

Tone Deaf, The Brag, J Play, The Industry Observer and Don’t Bore Us are all brands and publications under The Brag Media.

In the course of our activities Seventh Street Media Pty Ltd – trading as The Brag Media Australia – (The Brag Media, we, our, us) will collect, store, use, transfer and disclose personal information. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the personal information that you provide to us. This statement explains our policies and practices regarding the use, collection, storage and disclosure of your personal information by The Brag Media.

## Personal information

Personal information is information or an opinion about an identified individual, or an individual who is reasonably identifiable whether the information or opinion is true or not and whether the information is recorded in a material form or not.

## Types of personal information we collect and hold

The Brag Media collects and holds personal information about individuals for the provision of our products and services and purposes connected to those products and services.

Consistent with the provision or our products and services to you, the types of personal information The Brag Media may collect and hold about you include but are not limited to your name, address, telephone number, email address and financial information.

## How we collect and hold personal information

We may collect personal information directly from you in the course of providing our products and services from our website.

We collect your personal information when you register with us as a member or a subscriber, complete a survey, enter a competition, log a helpdesk request, visit any of our sites or when you initiate contact with us.

Even if you initially choose to subscribe to receive communications from us, you may also unsubscribe or resubscribe at a later stage.

For each visitor to our website, our server automatically recognises and stores the visitor’s IP address. In addition, our website uses cookies. Most web browsers are set by default to accept cookies. However, if you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to either prompt or refuse cookies. Please note that rejecting cookies will restrict the functionality of the website as a whole. We also use cookies for tracking the statistics of our website. This allows us to better understand our users and improve the layout and functionality of our website.

Personal information is held securely, is subject to various security protections and is held only for as long as the information remains relevant to the purpose for which it was collected.

We take all reasonable steps to protect the personal information that we hold from misuse, loss, or unauthorised access, including by means of firewalls, pass word access and secure servers. However, you acknowledge that the information you provide to us is at your own risk. We cannot accept responsibility for misuse or loss of, or unauthorised access to, your personal information where the security of information is not within our control.

You acknowledge that we are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of any third party (including third parties that we are permitted to disclose your personal information to in accordance with this policy or any applicable laws). The collection and use of your information by such third parties may be subject to separate privacy and security policies.

Our properties may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow you to contribute to market research, like Digital Content Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, please see the Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy at <https://priv-policy.imrworldwide.com/priv/browser/au/en/optout.html>

If you suspect any misuse or loss of, or unauthorised access to, your personal information, please contact our helpdesk immediately.

## Purposes for which we hold, use and disclose information

We hold use and disclose personal information.

The purposes for which we hold, use and disclose information include:

a) to communicate with you and provide you with the services you have requested;  
b) to enable your access to members-only features or services;  
c) to send marketing and promotional material that you have opted in to receive;  
d) to provide you with news and information about our products and services;  
e) to personalise and customise your experience;  
f) to conduct competitions;  
g) to verify your identity;  
h) to investigate any complaints about or made by you;  
i) to investigate breaches of our terms and conditions or other unlawful behaviour;  
j) other purposes as specified at the time of you supplying information to us;  
k) as required or permitted by any law (including the Privacy Act).

We may disclose personal information, and you consent to us disclosing your personal information, to third parties:

l) engaged by us to perform functions or provide products and services on our behalf;  
m) that are our agents, business partners or joint venture entities or partners;  
n) that sponsor or promote any competition that we conduct or promote;  
o) that are authorised by you to receive information held by us;  
p) if we have reason to suspect that you have committed a breach of our terms and conditions, or have otherwise been engaged in any unlawful activity;  
q) as part of a sale (or proposed sale) of all or part of our business; and/or  
r) as required or permitted by any law (including the Privacy Act).

## Access and correction

The Brag Media will take all reasonable steps to ensure any personal data we collect, use or disclose is up to date and accurate.

If you believe personal information we hold about you is not up to date or accurate, you may ask us to correct it.

You may ask us to provide you with details of the personal information we hold about you, and copies of that information. We will respond to your request and attempt to provide you with the data within 30 days of receipt of your request.

If we provide you with copies of the information you have requested, we may charge you a reasonable fee to cover the administrative costs of providing you with that information.

Please direct all request for access and correction to:

Privacy Officer  
The Brag Media  
Level 2, 9-13 Bibby Street  
Chiswick, NSW, 2046

## Overseas disclosure

The Brag Media may, in the course of providing products and services to you, disclose personal information to overseas entities. You agree that where personal information is disclosed to the countries above, the Australian Privacy Principles will not apply to that information.

## Changes to this policy

We will review and update this Privacy Policy from time to time as needed without notice. Therefore, you should review the terms of this policy periodically to make sure that you are aware of how we collect, hold, store and use personal information.

## Complaints

If you consider a breach of the Australian Privacy Principles has occurred, you may direct your query The Brag Media’s Privacy Officer and we will attempt to resolve your complaint.

If you do not consider our response satisfactory, you may contact the Australian Privacy Commissioner at its website www.oaic.giv.au or by telephone on 1300 363 992.
